A Guide to the Population Council records, Central Files, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 1 to Series 4 FA432
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, Central Files, 1957-1983; bulk; 2; 286 Cubic Feet
  - Foreign Correspondence File, 2; 72.72 Cubic Feet 164 document boxes.
    - El Salvador
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1960-1962 (Box 70, Folder 658)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1963-1972 (Box 70, Folder 659)
      - Asociacin Demogrfica Salvadorea, 1966-1972 (Box 70, Folder 660)
      - U. S. Agency for International Development, 1967-1970 (Box 70, Folder 661)
    - England
      England
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1959-1966 (Box 71, Folder 662)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 663)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 664)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 71, Folder 665)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 71, Folder 666)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Institute of Community Studies: Aerial Census, 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 667)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: R. Levin: Syntex Pharmaceuticals Ltd., 1968-1969 (Box 71, Folder 668)
      - Institute of Commonwealth Studies, 1960-1963 (Box 72, Folder 669)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation (I.P.P.F.), 1958-1964 (Box 72, Folder 670)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation (I.P.P.F.), 1965-1966 (Box 72, Folder 671)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation (I.P.P.F.), 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 672)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation (I.P.P.F.), 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 673)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation (I.P.P.F.), 1971-1973 (Box 72, Folder 674)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation (I.P.P.F.): Seventh International Conference on Planned Parenthood, Singapore, February 10-16, 1963, 1962-1963 (Box 72, Folder 675)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1961, 1967-1968, 1970-1972 (Box 72, Folder 676)
      - (The) London School of Economics and Political Science, 1958-1962, 1965-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 677)
      - (The) London School of Economics and Political Science: Dr. David Glass, 1959-1969, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 678)
      - (The) London School of Economics and Political Science: Population Investigation Committee, 1956, 1959-1965 (Box 73, Folder 679)
      - Redfern Polymers Ltd., 1967-1969 (Box 73, Folder 680)
      - University of Liverpool, 1967-1968, 1970-1973 (Box 73, Folder 681)
      - University of Liverpool: Dr. R. Mansell Prothero, 1959-1962, 1964-1965, 1969-1970, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 682)
      - University of Oxford: D. F. Roberts and R. E. S. Tanner, 1959-1963 (Box 73, Folder 683)
      - University of Sussex, 1966-1969 (Box 73, Folder 684)
      - University of Sussex: Population Seminar, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 685)
      - University of Sussex: Population Seminar, June 15-July 18, 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 73, Folder 686)
      - University of Sussex: Population Studies: Dudley Seers, 1966-1968 (Box 73, Folder 687)
    - Ethiopia
      Ethiopia
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1965-1973 (Box 74, Folder 688)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Habtu Eshete: Request for Demographer, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 689)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1969, 1972-1973 (Box 74, Folder 690)
      - United Nations Economic Commission for Africa, 1966-1971 (Box 74, Folder 691)
      - United Nations Economic Commission for Africa, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 692)
      - United Nations Economic Commission for Africa: Non-U. N. Organizations Interested in Population Work in Africa: Second Meeting, April 24-26, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 693)
      - United Nations Economic Commission for Africa: Non-U. N.Organizations Interested in Population Work in Africa: Third Meeting, May 7-9, 1973, 1971-1973 (Box 74, Folder 694)
      - United Nations Economic Commission for Africa: Tape Recorder Project: Dr. John Blacker and Christopher Scott, 1969-1970 (Box 74, Folder 695)
      - United Nations Economic Commission for Africa: Working Group on Fertility Levels and Differentials: Meeting, December 18-22, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 696)
      - U. S. Agency for International Development, 1967-1968, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 697)
    - Fiji
      Fiji
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1969-1970, 1972-1973 (Box 74, Folder 698)
      - Family Planning Association of Fiji, Inc., 1966-1970 (Box 74, Folder 699)
    - Finland
      Finland
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1966; 1971 (Box 74, Folder 700)
      - Finnish Population and Family Welfare League, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 701)
    - France
      France
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1959, 1961-1967 (Box 75, Folder 702)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1968-1970 (Box 75, Folder 703)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 75, Folder 704)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 705)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: 2nd European Population Conference, Strasbourg, August 31-September 7, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 706)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: cole Pratique des Hautes tudes, 1960-1961, 1964, 1966 (Box 75, Folder 707)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Institut National de la Statistique et des tudes Economiques, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 708)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Institut Social: Father S. de Lestapis, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 709)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development: Expert Group Meeting, April 1970 (Box 75, Folder 710)
      - Correspondence, Reports Studies: United Nations Expert Working Group on Population Research in National Institutions, Lyon, June 3-11, 1971, 1971-1972 (Box 75, Folder 711)
      - Institut National D'tudes Dmographiques, 1962-1965, 1967-1973 (Box 75, Folder 712)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 713)
    - Gambia
      Gambia
      - Report to the Government of the Gambia, Dr. John C. Caldwell, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 714)
    - Germany
      Germany
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1957-1958, 1960-1966 (Box 76, Folder 715)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967-1969 (Box 76, Folder 716)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1970-1971, 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 717)
      - Hochschule fr Internationale Pdagogische Forschung, 1961-1963 (Box 76, Folder 718)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1967-1968 (Box 76, Folder 719)
    - Ghana
      Ghana
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1966-1970 (Box 76, Folder 720)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1971-1975 (Box 76, Folder 721)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: 1960 Ghana Population Census, Volume V, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 722)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: African Population Conference, Accra, December 9-18, 1971, 1970-1972 (Box 76, Folder 723)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1963, 1968, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 724)
      - Dr. Benjamin Major, 1971-1972 (Box 77, Folder 725)
      - University of Ghana, 1960-1961; 1964-1974 (Box 77, Folder 726)
      - University of Ghana: Demographic Unit: Addo Project re: Birth and Death Registrations, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 727)
      - University of Ghana: Project Summary of the Danfa Rural Health and Family Planning Project, undated (Box 77, Folder 728)
      - University of Ghana: Research Proposal for Improvement of the Quality and Quantity of Socio-Demographic Data in Francophone West Africa: Dr. Tom Kumekpor, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 729)
      - U. S. Agency for International Development, 1967-1969, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 730)
      - U. S. Agency for International Development: Proposal for Research in Mortality in Ghana: Mr. Gaisie, 1967-1968 (Box 77, Folder 731)
    - Greece
      Greece
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1961-1970 (Box 77, Folder 732)
    - Guam
      Guam
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 77, Folder 733)
    - Guatemala
      Guatemala
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1962-1972 (Box 77, Folder 734)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 735)
      - Dr. Frederick J. Vintinner, 1966-1967 (Box 78, Folder 736)
      - Dr. Frederick J. Vintinner, 1968-1969 (Box 78, Folder 737)
    - Guinea
      Guinea
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 738)
    - Guyana
      Guyana
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 739)
    - Haiti
      Haiti
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1959, 1962, 1964-1967 (Box 78, Folder 740)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1968-1970 (Box 78, Folder 741)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1971-1973 (Box 78, Folder 742)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Centre D'Hygiene Familiale: Dr. Ary Bordes, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 743)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Louis Smith, 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 744)
      - Family Life Study: William Nibbling and J. Mayone Stycos, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 745)
      - Institut Haitien du Bien-Etre Social et de Recherches, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 746)
    - Honduras
      Honduras
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1965-1967, 1969-1972, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 747)
      - Asociacin Hondurea de Planificacin de Familia, 1964-1968, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 748)
      - Ministry of Public Health, 1965-1967, 1971-1972 (Box 79, Folder 749)
    - Hong Kong
      Hong Kong
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1962-1963, 1965-1971, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 750)
      - Ekder Plastic Works, 1968-1969 (Box 79, Folder 751)
      - Ekder Plastic Works, 1970-1971, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 752)
      - Family Planning Association of Hong Kong, 1958, 1960-1967 (Box 79, Folder 753)
      - Family Planning Association of Hong Kong, 1968-1972 (Box 79, Folder 754)
      - Family Planning Association of Hong Kong: Dr. K. C. Chan: Hong Kong Data, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 755)
      - Family Planning Association of Hong Kong: Grant Proposal: Robert W. Gillespie, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 756)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 757)
      - Project Concern, Inc., 1963-1966 (Box 80, Folder 758)
      - University of Hong Kong, 1961, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 759)
    - Hungary
      Hungary
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1965-1966, 1968-1969, 1971-1974 (Box 80, Folder 760)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: International Planned Parenthood Conference, Budapest, September 15-19, 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 761)
      - Hungarian Academy of Sciences: Committee for Demography: Central Statistical Office, 1961, 1963-1969 (Box 80, Folder 762)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 763)
    - India
      India
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1955-1963 (Box 80, Folder 764)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1964-1965 (Box 80, Folder 765)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 766)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 767)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 768)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1969 January-June (Box 81, Folder 769)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1969 July-December (Box 81, Folder 770)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 771)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 772)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 773)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 774)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 82, Folder 775)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Demographic Aspects of Labour Supply and Employment - Moderator's Statement, November 1972 (Box 82, Folder 776)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Forum International: International Action Corps Project, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 777)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: India Review 1974, 1970-1974 (Box 82, Folder 778)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: International Conference on Family Planning, New Delhi, January 23-27, 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 82, Folder 779)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: International Seminar on Maternal Mortality, Family Planning and Biology of Reproduction, Bombay, March 3-8, 1969, 1968-1971 (Box 82, Folder 780)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Khanna Population Study, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 781)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Pill Study, Bombay: Dr. S. D. Kanitkar and Dr. P. N. Shah, 1967-1968 (Box 82, Folder 782)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Visit of Dr. K. N. Rao, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 783)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Dr. Gerald Zatuchni: Report on Trip to India, June 12-20, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 784)
      - All-India Institute of Hygiene and Public Health, 1958-1965, 1968-1972 (Box 82, Folder 785)
      - All-India Institute of Hygiene and Public Health: Singur Study, 1955, 1957-1961, 1963-1965 (Box 83, Folder 786)
      - All India Institute of Medical Sciences, 1960-1968 (Box 83, Folder 787)
      - Calcutta Bacteriological Institute, 1960-1961 (Box 83, Folder 788)
      - Calcutta University, 1960-1961, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 789)
      - Central Drug Research Institute, 1960-1962, 1964, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 790)
      - Central Family Planning Institute, 1966-1970 (Box 83, Folder 791)
      - Central Health Education Bureau, 1961-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 83, Folder 792)
      - Demographic Training and Research Centre, 1967-1970, 1972-1973 (Box 83, Folder 793)
      - Directorate General of Health Services, Government of India: Lieutenant-Colonel B. L. Raina, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 794)
      - Directorate General of Health Services, Government of India: Lieutenant-Colonel B. L. Raina, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 795)
      - Directorate General of Health Services, Government of India: Lieutenant-Colonel B. L. Raina, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 796)
      - Directorate General of Health Services, Government of India: Lieutenant-Colonel B. L. Raina, 1961-1965 (Box 84, Folder 797)
      - Family Planning Association of India, 1962, 1966-1968, 1970, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 798)
      - Ford Foundation, 1961-1966 (Box 84, Folder 799)
        Includes correspondence with Dr. Katherine Kuder, Dr. Sheldon Segal, and Dr. Anna Southam.
      - Ford Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 800)
      - Ford Foundation, 1969-1972 (Box 84, Folder 801)
      - Ford Foundation: Dr. Douglas Ensminger, 1960-1963, 1965-1966 (Box 84, Folder 802)
      - Ford Foundation: Equipment Purchasing Program, 1962-1965 (Box 84, Folder 803)
      - Ford Foundation: Dr. Moye Freymann, 1960-1966 (Box 84, Folder 804)
      - Ford Foundation: Dr. David Price, 1965-1967 (Box 84, Folder 805)
      - Ford Foundation: Proposal for an Integrated Population Program in India, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 806)
      - Ford Foundation: Dr. Sheldon Segal, 1961-1963, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 807)
      - Gokhale Institute of Politics and Economics, 1957-1963, 1965-1966 (Box 85, Folder 808)
      - Gokhale Institute of Politics and Economics: Dr. (Mrs.) Kumudini Dandekar, 1958-1966, 1968, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 809)
      - Government Procedures, 1959-1965 (Box 85, Folder 810)
      - India-Harvard-Ludhiana Population Study, 1957-1960 (Box 86, Folder 811)
      - Indian Cancer Research Centre, 1959-1961 (Box 86, Folder 812)
      - Indian Institute of Management, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 813)
      - Indian Statistical Institute, 1958-1963, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 86, Folder 814)
      - Institute of Economic Growth, 1964, 1966, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 815)
      - Institute of Economic Research, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 816)
      - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1964-1966 (Box 86, Folder 817)
      - Jadavpur University, 1966-1967 (Box 86, Folder 818)
      - Jadavpur University: Dr. Ambica Ghosh, 1960-1963, 1965-1967, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 819)
      - Dr. Anrudh Jain, 1972-1973 (Box 86, Folder 820)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1967-1970, 1972, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 821)
      - Loyola College, 1961-1962, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 822)
      - Lucknow University, 1961-1962, 1965-1968 (Box 86, Folder 823)
      - Lucknow University: Dr. Radha Kamal Mukerjee, 1959, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 824)
      - Lucknow University: Dr. Baljit Singh, 1956-1959 (Box 86, Folder 825)
      - Ministry of Finance, Department of Economic Affairs, 1962, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 826)
      - Ministry of Health: Consultant: Harry L. Levin, 1965-1966 (Box 86, Folder 827)
      - Ministry of Health and Family Planning, 1965-1968 (Box 87, Folder 828)
        Includes correspondence with Dr. Katherine Kuder.
      - Ministry of Health and Family Planning, 1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 829)
      - Peace Corps, 1967-1969 (Box 87, Folder 830)
      - Personnel, 1958-1959 (Box 87, Folder 831)
      - Pollachi Institute of Demographic Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 87, Folder 832)
      - Registrar General: Ministry of Home Affairs, 1958-1961 (Box 87, Folder 833)
      - Registrar General: Ministry of Home Affairs, 1962-1964, 1966-1969, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 834)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1961-1967 (Box 87, Folder 835)
      - Dr. Maung Sein, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 836)
      - United Nations: Commission to India, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 837)
      - United Nations: Economic Commission for Asia and the Far East (ECAFE): "Fertility and Family Planning Evaluation" Training Course, Bombay, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 838)
      - University of Bombay, 1957-1961, 1964-1966, 1968-1973 (Box 87, Folder 839)
      - University of California: Dr. William Griffiths and Dr. Beryl Roberts, 1959-1960 (Box 88, Folder 840)
      - University of Delhi, 1958-1962, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 841)
      - University of Delhi: Family Planning Unit, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 842)
      - University of Kerala, 1959-1964, 1970 (Box 88, Folder 843)
      - University of Kerala: Dr. (Miss) A. George: Calculators, 1967-1969 (Box 88, Folder 844)
      - U. S. Agency for International Development, 1966-1974 (Box 88, Folder 845)
      - Vasectomy, 1969, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 846)
      - Virus Research Centre, 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 847)
      - World Conference on Medical Education, 1966 (Box 88, Folder 848)
      - Dr. Gerald Zatuchni, 1969-1971 (Box 88, Folder 849)
    - Indonesia
      Indonesia
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1957-1960 (Box 88, Folder 850)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1961-1966 (Box 89, Folder 851)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 852)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1968-1969 (Box 89, Folder 853)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 89, Folder 854)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 855)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: English Language Training, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 856)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: World Bank Mission: Report of March 24, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 857)
      - Dinas Geografi, 1961-1963, 1965-1967 (Box 89, Folder 858)
      - Family Planning Clinics Project: IUD Study, 1964-1966 (Box 89, Folder 859)
      - Fellowships: Widjojo Nitisastro, 1956-1961 (Box 89, Folder 860)
      - Ford Foundation, 1967-1971, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 861)
      - Dr. Gavin Jones, 1969-1974 (Box 90, Folder 862)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1964, 1967-1970, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 863)
      - John Laing, 1973, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 864)
      - M.I.P.I. (Council for Sciences of Indonesia), 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 865)
      - M.I.P.I. (Council for Sciences of Indonesia): Equipment, 1960-1961, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 866)
      - M.I.P.I. (Council for Sciences of Indonesia): Dr. Halvor Gille, 1959-1964 (Box 90, Folder 867)
      - M.I.P.I. (Council for Sciences of Indonesia): Dr. R. H. Pardoko, 1961-1965 (Box 90, Folder 868)
      - M.I.P.I. (Council for Sciences of Indonesia): Reports, 1963, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 869)
      - M.I.P.I. (Council for Sciences of Indonesia): Dr. Prawirohardjo Sarwono, 1959-1963 (Box 90, Folder 870)
      - M.I.P.I. (Council for Sciences of Indonesia): Dr. R. Wasito, 1959-1962, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 871)
      - Planned Parenthood Association, 1959; 1967-1968; 1970-1971 (Box 90, Folder 872)
    - Iran
      Iran
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1960-1961, 1964-1966 (Box 91, Folder 873)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 91, Folder 874)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 91, Folder 875)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1971 January-October (Box 91, Folder 876)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1971 November-December (Box 91, Folder 877)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 878)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 879)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Basic Agreement, 1971-1973 (Box 92, Folder 880)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Customs and Excise Duties, 1968-1971 (Box 92, Folder 881)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Population Projections, February 1972 (Box 92, Folder 882)
      - Dr. Morris Dixon: 1967 Iran Trips, 1967 April-September (Box 92, Folder 883)
      - Dr. Morris Dixon: 1967 Iran Trips, 1967 September (Box 92, Folder 884)
      - Dr. Morris Dixon: 1967 Iran Trips, 1967 October-December (Box 92, Folder 885)
      - Dr. Morris Dixon: 1968 Iran Trip (Box 93, Folder 886)
      - Dr. Morris Dixon: 1969 Iran Trip (Box 93, Folder 887)
      - Dr. Morris Dixon: 1970 Iran Trip (Box 93, Folder 888)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 889)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1969 January-May (Box 93, Folder 890)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1969 June-December (Box 93, Folder 891)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1970 January-March (Box 93, Folder 892)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1970 April-December (Box 93, Folder 893)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1971 January=September (Box 93, Folder 894)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1971 October-December (Box 94, Folder 895)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 896)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen: Fars Project, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 897)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen: Management Consulting, 1971-1972 (Box 94, Folder 898)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen: NESA Proposals, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 899)
      - Robert Gillespie, 1970-1971 (Box 94, Folder 900)
      - Robert Gillespie, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 901)
      - Robert Gillespie, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 902)
      - International Congress on Tropical Medicine and Malaria, Tehran, September 7-15, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 903)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1966-1972, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 904)
      - Ministry of Health, 1966-1967 (Box 95, Folder 905)
      - Ministry of Health, 1968 January-April (Box 95, Folder 906)
      - Ministry of Health, 1968 May-December (Box 95, Folder 907)
      - Ministry of Health, 1969-1971 (Box 95, Folder 908)
      - Ministry of Health, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 909)
      - Ministry of Health, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 910)
      - Ministry of Health: Central Evaluation Unit, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 911)
      - Pahlavi University, 1966-1968, 1970, 1972-1974 (Box 96, Folder 912)
      - University of Tehran, 1964, 1967-1970, 1972-1974 (Box 96, Folder 913)
      - University of Tehran: Faculty of Hygiene and Public Health, 1971-1974 (Box 96, Folder 914)
      - University of Tehran: Institute for Social Studies and Research, 1959, 1961, 1964-1967 (Box 96, Folder 915)
      - U. S. Agency for International Development, 1968-1969 (Box 97, Folder 916)
      - Dr. Gerald Zatuchni, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 917)
    - Iraq
      Iraq
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1962-1965, 1969-1971 (Box 97, Folder 918)
    - Israel
      Israel
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1956, 1958, 1960-1963, 1965-1972 (Box 97, Folder 919)